## Vlad-Cristian Puscaru

 ♥ Utrecht, Utrecht, Netherlands
 ■ vlad.cpuscaru@gmail.com
 □ +40736167606
 ■ in/vlad-cristian-puscaru-2399b6123

vladpuscaru.github.io/portfolio-website/

## **SUMMARY**

Software Engineer from Romania with 5+ years of experience and demonstrated abilities in multiple areas of development. My main interests revolve around web, cloud, games and embedded development.

Have a look at my portfolio webpage for recent relevant projects.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Software Developer & Team Lead

EDAM

April 2022 - August 2023, Remote

- · Building solutions and conducting maintenance for one of the biggest video game companies in the world (Epic Games)
- · Leading a team of 5 developers
- $\cdot$  Being a mentor and technology expert

## **Game Developer**

Metwander - Contract based

April 2022 - June 2022, Remote

- · Building a Virtual Reality video game prototype for an upcoming cryptocurrency
- · Creating and managing multiple aspects of game development (gameplay, networking, avatar rigging and animation)

#### Software Developer & Team Lead

**Deloitte Digital** 

April 2020 - April 2022, Romania, Bucharest

- · Key developer in one of the impactful projects at a national level COVID-19 digital solution for the National Health Service (NHS) UK
- · Leading a team of 7 developers

#### Junior Web Developer

**Quart Creative Agency** 

September 2018 - March 2019, Romania, Bucharest

- · Delivering custom web solutions, based on given design mock-ups
- · Creating in-house tools used by the entire team

#### **EDUCATION**

## MSc Game and Media Technology

Utrecht University · Netherlands, Utrecht

· I am back to school in order to specialise and research in game development-related areas such as graphics, physics, crowd simulation

#### **BSc Economic Informatics**

Academy of Economic Studies, Bucharest · Romania, Bucharest · 2020

• Final score of 10/10, with the thesis "IoT Solution for Smart Home"

## **Software Development - Private Courses**

STEP IT Academy · Romania, Bucharest · 2019

- · Software Development courses at a private institution
- · Curricula included: C, C++, C#, Algorithms, and Design Patterns

#### INVOLVEMENT

#### **Student Ambassador**

 $\textbf{Utrecht University} \cdot \textbf{Utrecht University} \cdot \textbf{September 2023 - Present}$ 

- · Actively speak with prospect students, answering questions and providing guidance
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$  Participate in public events, such as University Open Days

## Member / Treasurer / Vice President

Rotaract • Rotaract District 2241 • July 2016 - Present

• Honorable mention: Being in charge of the Logistics Department in one of the biggest district level projects in Romania, called "O cana de fericire".

# **SKILLS**

- C,C++,C#
   Javascript, Typescript, NodeJS, ReactJS
   AWS, Docker, Azure
   Graphics Programming, Algorithms
   Project Mangament